JI-YANG LIN

MASTER STUDENT

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Energetic and passionate master student and aiming to use my knowledge that I have aquired from 1 year experience in software work and coursework and with my hard work to satisfy my intership at your organization and also willing to learn more from this intership.

STRENGTHS

Open minded

Motivated

Creative

Leadership

Team player

Time management

Fast, passionate learner

SKILLS

Programming Language

Python ★★★
Java ★★★
JavaScript ★★
C/C++ ★★
Swift ★

Web Technologies:

Front-End: ★★★

HTML, Javascript, jQuery, CSS, Bootstrap Proficient in Liferay framwork Skilled in React.js,

Data visualization

Back-End: ★★

Proficient in SQL, SSMS Skilled in MVC, MVT framwork

DevOps ★★

Software Engineering Intermediate in Data Structures, Algorithms Skilled in Scrum/Agile/Git/ Jira/ SVN

Learning

Golang Django Jenkins

Docker

Deep Learning Implement

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer | 04.2019 -03.2020

Applications Developing Dept. in Lianhwa Foods Corporation

• Brainstroms the system architecture and review developing routine with team member.

Mobile: (886) 0975179121 Email: xuunnis123@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/ji-yanglin Blog: medium.com/@xuunnis1011

Note: https://hackmd.io/@EzraLin Github: github.com/xuunnis123

- Response for developing full-stack website, using Liferay MVC framework, and designing database.
- Project: Electronic Invoice System Upload Automation, Materialchecked with Portable devices, Semi-finished products Record System, Shopee API Plugin, and so on.

Keywords: software development, full-stack website, git/SVN, Jira, Java, bootstrap, SQL, database, Liferay framework

Arduino Robots Tutor | 04.2019 - 06.2019

Shih-Yu High School, New Taipei City

- Taught high school students Arduino Robots every week.
- Helped students to solve coding problem.

Keywords: Arduino Robot, Teaching experience, Arduino

Fullstack Website Engineering Intern | 12.2018-02.2019

Ru-San Logistics Company, Taipei

• Developed full-stack website with Spring MVC framework.

Keywords: Fullstack Website programming, Co-work

iOS developing, Calculus Teaching assistant | 07.2018-01.2019

National Taiwan Ocean University, Keelung Keywords: iOS, Swift, Code Review

President | 2017-2018

Computer Science Class B of National Taiwan Ocean University, Keelung

Vice President | 2016-2017

Humanities and Social Science Camp for high school student, Chiayi Keywords: Leadership, Teamwork, Crisis management

EDUCATION HIGHLIGHTS

National Central University

Master in Computer Science | 09.2021 - est. 06.2023

- Major in artificial intelligence
- Lab in Knowledge System Lab, which cooperates with Kyoto University, uses big data and deep learning technology to track and to predict how student's performance.

National Taiwan Ocean University

Bachelor in Computer Science | 09.2015 - 01.2019

- GPA: 3.6/4.0
- Class Valedictorian-Graduation Ceremony
- Bachelor degree project, Spine Reminder, fields in iOT with Android app.
- Fourth place of fourteen teams, Smart technologies Innovation and Pioneer competition, 2018